GRADEY CULLINS



@ gradeycullins@gmail.com

github.com/GradeyCullins

Seasoned computer programmer with a hunger for growth and success. Demonstrable track record highlighting a broad variety of hard and soft skills related to professional computing. Professional experience ranging from established corporate environments to disruptive startups.

EXPERIENCE

Lead Software Engineer at Radom

Aug 2021 - December 2022

Lead a small **Agile** development team to develop an Ethereum-based full-stack decentralized application **(dApp)** with **Vue.js**, **React.js**, **typescript**, **Solidity**, **Rust**, and **Figma**. Work with founders to implement the product vision and plan development objectives for developers. Direct, mentor, and review junior developers' code. Architected and "owned" the front-end. Design, implement, and test features across the tech stack including front-end features and Solidity code. Direct implementation of advanced Solidity "Diamond" concept for advanced Solidity contract.

Software Engineer at Hoodoo

Jan 2018 - Jan 2021

Full stack programmer with multiple responsibilities across front and backend technology. Develop and maintain: SPA with **Vue.js**, command-line tool **(CLI)** tool with **Node.js**, REST API server in **GoLang**. Write dockerfiles to deploy SPA and API server in **Kubernetes** in **AWS EKS**, and onpremises hosting environments. Engage with clients and help onboard with full-stack software suite (described above).

Front-end Developer at Western Digital

May 2019 - Sep 2019

Temporary contract role while full-time at Hoodoo to develop pixel-perfect westerndigital.com site. Translate Figma designs into mobile-first responsive website with **Vue.js**.

Full-stack Web Developer at Navitaire

May 2017 - Jan 2018

Full stack web developer on **Scrum Agile** team making e-commerce web app in **Angular JS**, **C#/.NET**, and **MSSQL**. Contribute to internal testing GUI tool in **C#**. Spearhead automated testing system with **Postman CLI** and **Powershell scripts**.

EDUCATION

B.S. Computer Science at University of Utah

2013-2018

PROJECTS

Purity Vision

Open-source <u>Chrome browser extension</u> and <u>GoLang API Server</u> utilizing Google's Machine Learning Vision API to filter explicit images from untrusted webpages.